but this right here is going to put the
biggest smile on my face the biggest
this right here is my
new masterpiece it's week four of me
turning $100 into a Million last week we
were trying to turn $3,000 up to
$6,000 the account is currently sitting
at $3,000 and at the beginning of the
week as soon as we took the trade we
almost blew the
account this seem
good but luckily the entry was very
precise and we had very well takeprofit
setup and we ended up closing the
account at $115,000 in profit all right
market update is literally 30 minutes
later we are still in the trade so now
we're up
$5,500 so double the profit of what we
originally set for ourselves for that
week now that leaves us with a starting
balance for this week of $155,000 now
the goal for this week is to take
$155,000 to $30,000 this is week four of
turning $100 into a all right ladies and
gentlemen welcome to
day it's Day Zero cuz tomorrow's day one
tomorrow's day one well it's not day one
cuz it's we're [__] week four of the
challenge dude so we're on like probably
day like 20 we're cuz we're on week four
whatever it's day one of the week So
currently right now it is drum roll
please Sunday whoa Monday Monday
midnight so it literally just became
Monday 6 minutes ago Miami time right so
but it's technically Sunday night so
currently right now the account is at
$115,000 we have not taken any trades
just yet so let me share with you guys
the markets that we're going to be
trading this week so like always Let me
refresh the page what time is it right
now Miami it's August 5th 12 a.m. so
let's start off the markets this week so
last week we had a very successful week
we turned $3,000 to
$115,000 now this goal's week is to turn
$15,000 to $30,000
[__] and honestly I think it's very
possible because there's some really
good opportunities if we miss one of
these opportunities I think we won't
have a trade this week but just looking
you know based off of my experience in
the markets so first trade that we're
interested in taking is going to be AUD
CAD AUD CAD right now on the daily time
frame we are very much bearish the daily
time frame has had a very strong move to
the downside retest this level sold
broken this level retested it this is
clearly a level of support one above and
a level of support one above if we
continue to look left here you can see
that it is clearly resistance went under
so if we follow the same line we can
tell that we're clearly under so we're
looking to pretty much so weekly time
frame has had a very strong push to the
downside we're bearish we're under the
structure level and the weekly time
frame is under this and then it's under
this we also have a weekly Doe so we can
easily fill out dogee to the downside
but now we go to the 4our time frame and
at the 4H hour time frame we have a very
very clear uh shift the structure right
now this has clearly gone bearish well
it is bearish it's lower high lower low
but in this structure we have shifted
and on the 1H hour time frame we have
had a beautiful left head right shoulder
retest of the neckline and then now it
looks like we are selling if you guys
notice every single trade we have taken
thus far has had this head and shoulders
pattern which works AB absolutely
beautifully and this trade looks like we
just missed it because it's having the
rejection I wanted to enter earlier but
rule of thumb I do not take trades on
Sunday night so I need take trades on
Monday morning London session so
technically in about an hour but it
looks like this trade is already moving
that fast but I'm going to stick to my
plan and not take any trades until then
simply because statistically proven over
the last thousand trades that I've taken
taking trades on Sunday night it's not a
deal trade will hit your stop loss
because the market has to create that
Weekly Wick but I'll explain that
probably in another video so what we
were looking for is for price to come
back and retest this EMA retest the
Nightline of The Head and Shoulders to
them sell we're looking to get an entry
right around up here but it looks like
it has already rejected and kind of
sucks so there's not much I can do I
don't really want to chase the trade and
then put a stop loss like this cuz then
my First Take profit would have to be
this point and then obviously if that's
my first take profit that is a shitty
ass risk of reward if this is my second
take profit it's decent but I still
don't want to have a stop loss that is
like that tight and does not give me
enough breathing room so for this trade
we're just going to Simply wait for it
up here I'm going to put an alarm to see
just in case if it does have some type
of retracement next is going to be GBP
CAD so GBP CAD we've been watching this
trade since probably the last three
weeks of the challenge last weekly
Candlestick we officially had a
humongous weekly dogee and I strongly do
believe that this week we're going to
fail that Wick cuz we have created a
high higher low higher high now I do
believe we can come back into this area
to create a higher low simply continue
heading to the upside so we are taking a
counter Trend trade and the daily time
frame is clearly beish we have high low
high low high boom broke structure so
now we are bearish we are rejecting
round olical level 177 500 and then on
the 4H hour time frame we are right
around under that 4H hour EMA and that
round psychological level what I'm going
be waiting for now on this trade is
simply a break and retest under this
area of interest for price to then be
ready pretty much to sell I don't want
to sell within this box cuz clearly when
we're selling into the box it's
rejecting up when we're in the Box it's
rejecting up but when we're under the
box it is setting down so I want to wait
for it to get under the box in order for
us to be interested in selling I am a
master at these boxes I've been putting
these boxes on for [__] ever so
that's GBP CAD next Euro USD funny
enough last week we were looking to sell
at this head and shoulders pattern left
head right shoulder retest to then sell
and now this week we're actually
interested in buying so this shows you
guys that we react and adapt to what the
market shows us and the different
opportunities that it has to offer so
here we have a very strong push to the
upside and now we're looking to have a
retest of this level to then continue to
buy the 4-Hour time frame has very
clearly broken out of what looks to be a
very strong bearish Channel I hate using
trend lines but it's very obvious this
wasn't a bearish channel we broke out of
it now what we have to be patient for is
this pullback so then we buy so we're
just waiting on price to basically have
this pullback so we can take this
straight to the upside so we have our
risk to reward tool ready to go and we
have our pullback predictions ready to
go so for now we got to set and forget
next is Euro GBP Euro GBP is very
similar to Euro USD we are clearly
bullish we've had a very strong push to
the upside this is what this Market
essentially looks like right now we've
had a very strong push and obviously you
can't buy all the way up here yeah you
have to wait for a pull back to then buy
and if I just bring this back over here
it's exactly how it looks like we have
the push to the upside now we're just
going to wait for this retest to head to
the upside on this level of support
support and support clearly whenever
above or rejecting up so right now we
got to wait for it to pull back and on
the process of this having this pull
back to this level the EMA is also going
to then have this little retracement
here so then it could get used as
support to then head to the upside next
is going to be
gbpusd so gbpusd is a little bit more
clean on the 4our and it's basically I'm
predicting for this to do the exact same
thing as your USD now keep in mind this
is something that comes with experience
this is because I've seen this hundreds
of times and I simply can kind of almost
tell when it's going to happen again but
pay attention so you guys can notice the
resemblance one pair versus the other so
let me show you guys so right now gbpusd
it is in this downwards Channel or what
it looks like to be this bearish Channel
and if you notice on EUR USD it's
exactly what we had right here if you
notice they look pretty much [__]
identical but what happened with your
USD it broke out of that bearish channel
now in gbpusd we haven't quite broken
out of that channel so my prediction is
for price to break out of this channel
retest it and then head to the upside so
technically Euro USD is ahead because it
already broke out our waiting is for the
retest to go long GDP USD we haven't
broken out yet but that's my prediction
I'm looking for it to break out of this
channel so then it can continue heading
to the upside and then last but not
least is going to be Euro AUD and Euro
AUD is very simple we're at a higher
high of this Market I'm just waiting for
a retest of this level to then continue
this trade to the upside then that I get
any more textbook but clearly a very
strong level of resistance resistance
resistance support resistance resistance
resistance whenever we're under a
rejecting or whenever we're above
rejecting very clean break and retest
pair so for now AUD CAD is pretty much
the one that is ready essentially right
now and it looks like it's already
having the movement so the only way I'll
be interested in taking the trade once
we have that pullback so it's pretty
much it probably long
explanation damn that [__] took 7
minutes to [__] explain but just
market update phone doesn't have battery
currently right now it is is 12:14 at
night so I'll probably wake up 7:8 in
the morning and we'll see you guys then
to see what the market has done see you
guys tomorrow in the morning all right
good morning ladies and gentlemen what
an interesting morning Lally the first
thing that I woke up to is my phone
blowing up the market crash Bitcoin
crashed dark Market is
crashing this is something that I called
a really long time ago simply because it
just doesn't make sense when everything
is so high like things could go up for a
really long time but not for forever
everything always needs a correction the
Mark is always over do a correction so
just to show you guys right now well
before anything this is what matters 100
to the mill account we are literally
exactly the same no trades have been
taken it is currently 9:00 in the
morning so 8:55 in the morning just to
show you guys over here once again this
is where we refreshed it yesterday so
it's 900 in the morning so now this
Bitcoin Bitcoin crashed today in the
morning as soon as the market I guess
opened Bitcoin has had his amazing major
move this is the weekly time frame my
predictions have always been for price
to come back and retest this level of
resistance and resistance before heading
to the upside yes my strategy has worked
in crypto previously we got some
beautiful buys down here which is
absolutely amazing but now to what
matters which is the 100 to the mill
count trade so if you guys remember last
night or for you guys a couple of
seconds ago literally I was explaining
how I was looking to enter this trade if
it would have had a little bit of a
pullback into this area so then I can
take the sell price never pulled back
and we missed out on this major major
Market move it had the [__] perfect
retest of this everything exactly
explained perfectly and we simply missed
it because the trade was not at the
minor area we wanted it to go to now
this is going to happen to us time and
time again it's normal it's inevitable
this is the importance of having a
trading strategy now sometimes you miss
these trades sometimes you catch them
what do I change in order to continue to
catch them nothing because then that's
going to affect my win rate on the ones
that I should have catched and this is
where a lot of you guys make mistakes
you're going to miss trades it's okay
[__] happens was a big deal didn't cost
you anything now you have to wait for
the next trade to pop up just like this
one which there is one popping up so
this trade AUD CAD sadly it has [__]
left and we have missed it it is what it
is we'll catch another trade this if we
would have entered up here we would have
easily caught in right now A 1 to six
which is crazy next gvp CAD gvp
CAD this trade right here we explained
it last night that we were looking for
price to have the break and then the
retest to then sell it's exactly what we
did uh the trade kind of left as well
didn't have the retest as much as I
wanted to but it is what it is I
explained that the weekly time frame has
to fill that Wick it's exactly what
we're doing right now so we missed out
on this trade as well the market has
been very very volatile right now
there's just a lot of fundamentals
pushing price but didn't reach it
exactly how I wanted to even if I go
down to the lower time frame like 30
minute I guess this is it right here but
N I would have not even really counted
it next is Euro USD so Euro USD we've
been waiting for a retracement to this
area to then continue heading to the
upside no retracement price just
continued going to the upside so we
could not take this trade Euro GBP same
exact thing last night we were at this
point and we wanted her price to have a
pullback to then head to the upside but
we did not catch any trades on this
point gbpusd had a little bit of a push
to then the bottom of this kind of
downwards Channel and now it's retesting
this level of support and resistance
that is clearly very well respected
throughout here so I can't take a trade
in here we want to take a trade as soon
as it so it it it's been exactly as I
drew out I drew this out right so price
was here when Market open we wanted to
retest this area then have a breakout
then have a retest and then this is
where we would enter so it's literally
following the plan that I anticipated
for it I just can't enter the trade here
I want to enter the trade once it breaks
and retests out and uh last but not
least Euro AUD we anticipated for price
to come back and retest this level but
it just flew so the only trades that I
available kind of somewhat soon it's
going to be
gbpusd and then maybe GBP CAD all right
so basically GBP USD and GBP CAD so GBP
CAD I just need for price to have a
little retracement so this just
confirmed closed right now on the 4our
like this so the 4-Hour time frame just
closed bearish engulfing like that which
is phenomenal but I think we should have
a little retracement on at least the 1
hour for price to just create real
structure so then here's what we would
look for our entry to then take this
trade to the downside just needed to
create something like this left head and
then this right shoulder so we can sell
so GBP CAD would be the one that we're
interested in taking and then gbpusd cuz
we actively missed AUD cat which [__]
sucks but you guys are seeing it
firsthand how simple strategy Works what
did you guys thr out today all right
guys market update it is currently 8:00
in the afternoon as you guys can see the
weather today has been trash as you guys
can see it's been literally raining this
we're in the [__] middle of a
hurricane right now we're Floridians we
don't care about a hurricane but I don't
want to drive any of the cars in the
rain cuz [__] gets thrown on the road I
don't want to pop a tire just anything
so the rain stopped so now we're going
to go hit the gym literally been stuck
home all day because of the rain so let
me actually show you the markets so
right now on AUD CAD exactly what I
explained earlier we had a very strong
rejection from the neckline of The Head
and Shoulders we had the beautiful cell
this is where we would have entered we
would have gotten out this is what I
explained to you guys earlier you cannot
enter on just the price having a
pullback and you want to ENT enter an
impulsive cell it simply does not make
any sense just because the move happened
and now it's having a pullback you
cannot enter an impulsive sell on a
trade that does not have any entry
confirmations you cannot treat this
trade right here with no confirmation as
if it were to be this trade right here
just because the market had a push from
this level of resistance to the downside
it makes absolutely no [__] sense so
this is where a lot of mistakes were
being made in the Discord earlier today
with the students and I was literally
explaining to them like guys you can't
treat you can't treat a pullback as if
it were to be the same entry as the
actual trade that we took and that's a
big mistake that a lot of people were
making just because they missed out on
the first entry they felt like they had
to get into the second one and for those
of them that did they lost so I didn't
get in because obviously I was waiting
for I treat every single trade different
I can't treat this entry as if it were
to be the same as this one so now as
it's having to pull back it's retesting
this neckline I am going to be waiting
for the break and structure of this 30
minute higher low time frame so
basically I'm going to be waiting for
the same thing I did here higher high
higher low higher high it broke retested
this is the entry missed it now I'm just
going to be waiting for the same thing
here to enter the trade to the downside
and just to show you guys right now
there is no entries into the trade right
now the account is exactly the same
we're currently at
$155,000 and we have not entered any
trades so this is just AUD CAD we're
going to be waiting for this break and
retest to enter the trade so next Market
is going to be gbpusd which we are still
inside of this channel just waiting for
the breakout retest to head to the
upside Euro GBP we've had an absolutely
extremely strong bullish day just
waiting for a retest to head to the
upside GBP CAD on the other hand we have
a beautiful confirmation that we have
rejected this retest of the shifter
structure rejection from the round
psychological level
77500 and then on the 4H hour we can see
that it's starting to head a little bit
up but not quite where we needed in
order to enter the trade so I'm going to
be waiting for price to retest this EMA
and this area and where my alarm is
honestly in order for me to enter the
trade so earlier this morning we had
this line which we wanted to break we
were had the break now we're just
waiting for the retest for it to then
sell and then last but not least we have
Euro USD which we've had the break out
of the channel now we're just waiting
for the retest to head to the upside so
the main ones that I'm only focused on
is going to the AUD CAD for an entry
after it has this shift because the
daily does look very nice with this
humongous daily DOI I am a lover of
these daily dois because I am a firm
believer that they always get filled
especially when you have the daily time
frame bearish and the 4our time frame
bearish and the weekly time frame
bearish so I'm just going to be waiting
for my entry confirmation I'm going to
put my little alarm right around here
just to let me know that it's breaking
that level and have an alarm here just
in case it decides to go a little bit
higher and then GBP CAD once it has this
pool back here then I'll be interested
in selling so once again market update
8:05 in the afternoon after this we're
going to go hit the gym get back in the
gym I've been slacking can't even lie
just haven't been feeling the motivation
we're [__] getting back
[Music]
in see what's going to go on
oh
[Music]
oh oh
so right now GBP CAD still waiting for
it to have a pullback hasn't had the
pullback quite yet a cad it's having the
first anal
rejection we're waiting for the break
under that structure level right there
so that might happen soon I might
enter I don't know if this 4H hour
Candlestick engulf the next two and two
and a half hours I'll enter the TR for
right now you guys can clearly see no
one trades in the
account so you guys all right guys what
is going on so market update it is
currently 1 in the morning so as you
guys can see it is 1:11 in the morning
not sure if you guys can see it there
there you go so right now trade did not
close under the area that we wanted to
so I literally stayed up to 1:00 in the
morning for no [__] reason and the
problem is that I'm so invested at this
point that I think I'm just going to
have to stay up to like 3:00 in the
morning waiting for this trade to play
out let me actually show you guys what I
mean So currently this is AUD CAD as you
guys can see right here we're waiting
for price to have the pull back here and
then the Candlestick to body close under
it did not we go down to the 1 hour we
did not have a break of structure we go
down to the 30 minute we did not have a
break of structure so we're still just
waiting we we could take the trade here
it's not a bad trade it's just a little
bit of a highrisk trade so the reason
why say we got to wait until 3:00 in the
morning is because that might be the
momentum that's going to give us that
break at that point but I might enter
before I don't know I don't know so for
this next 4H hour Candlestick to then
close we got to wait another 4 hours 3
hours and 47 minutes so let's see we
might enter the trade we might not but
I'll keep you guys updated if not I just
might fall asleep all right guys market
update it is currently 9:58 in the
morning pretty much 10: in the morning
as you guys can see we are locked in so
the account right now we have no traits
and we have not had the execution on AUD
PAD as we wanted to so I'm locked in as
you guys can see my chair is facing
forward my feet are on the little thingy
so I am locked the [__] in let me
explain to you guys right here so
yesterday we set this 30 minutes shift
the structure level so price from where
we were rejecting from decided to have
another pullback then lendon session and
did go and it finally broke the
structure so now we're having the pull
back into this area and then here where
we're actually looking to enter so I
just have my R reward tool there doesn't
mean that I actually am looking to enter
the trade there we had the shift of
structure we shifted the structure and
now we're having the pull back now and
here I need to wait for the engulfing on
this market so all I have to do is just
wait so this going to happen in the next
I don't know 30 minutes 40 minutes I
have no idea what I do know is that it
is moving I like leaving this here cuz
it shows me how much it's moving I think
it's going to come in reject that EMA
and reject that structure level GB P CAD
is crazy the fact that we've been
predicting this ship for I don't like
we've been predicting this move right
here specifically since we were up here
we had the left head right shoulder pop
up a clip of gvp Cad and you can see
right here on the 4our time frame we are
literally lining up a left head and then
a right shoulder to where this Market we
can then have a break a retest to then
sell to the downside and then retest
this neckline of the EMA 2 weeks ago
we've been looking at this person since
we started the challenge and we waiting
for this specific trade and we [__]
missed it and and it it sucks because
it's going to happen you're going to
dude you're going to look at markets and
you're going to wait for a trade to play
out to get to your area of interest for
2 weeks and it's going to get to that
area of interest and it's going to give
you the entry signal and you fell asleep
and you missed it but then you know what
you're going to stay trading so you're
going to wait for it again right another
trade comes up you're going to wait 2
weeks for it going to get to your area
area of interest it's going to get give
your entry your entry signal and as soon
as you take the trade straight to your
stop loss you're going to wait 2 weeks
to miss a trade then you're going to
wait 2 weeks to then lose a trade it's
just how it [__] works now because I
missed this trade this doesn't mean
anything it doesn't mean that now I have
to change something in my strategy or I
have to uh add something new no I simply
just missed it now I just wait for New
Opportunities so let me show you guys
literally we were waiting for this trade
to pull back into this area right here
to then sell
never did it we had the movement
perfectly as we anticipated we've had
this High we had the pullback literally
everything that I've been predicting on
this pair for such a long time literally
we've been looking at this Market before
it even created this red Candlestick
right when it created this first one so
we've been looking at this market for 3
weeks and it had to move and it is what
it is we simply just missed it there's
nothing that we can do we just take the
same approach to a different market and
wait for it to play out
gbpusd we still have not broken out of
this channel clearly we rejected the top
of it and now we're at the bottom of the
channel once again we got to wait for
that break and retest to go long Euro
GBP looks like we are starting to have a
Slowdown but still no pullback and then
Euro USD looks like it is starting to
having that pullback so we just got to
wait for price to retest this area down
here to then enter the trade so this is
actually going to the top of my watch
list because we got to wait for it to
reach this area to then buy just how it
did here just how it did here so we got
to wait for it to make it there and then
AUD cat is just the first one that I'd
be interested in taking the trade so we
are currently right now waiting for this
Candlestick to reject so s and forget
boys we'll update you guys in 30 45
minutes 10: in the morning right now all
right so we just got well actually trade
update it is currently 2:00 in the
afternoon markets haven't even moved
I'll show you guys right now what's
going on but our Atlanta just pulled up
so Atlanta just did a collap with Trump
where he pulled up he actually signed
one of the paintings that he did I
actually have a bunch of artlanta paint
throughout my whole entire house but I
just got two new posters going to give
one to one of my family members are all
about Trump and I want to put one on the
wall CU I think this is a legendary ass
picture and then ARA did it herself
let's
go oh [__] so this K's in a frame and
everything you got the first two
literally the first
two so that's that's basically where he
sign it on the on the original one yeah
but this that's my signature oh okay so
yeah but he said it like somewhere
exactly yeah okay so oh wait so this is
one out of 47 one and that's two and two
out of 47 oh [__] so I got the real
first oh
[__] appreciate you bro this lit so so
what's this yeah this I got to get the
the folders in the car I'm put it like
in the folder for you oh [__] dope we
got one out of 470 and then this one's
two out of 470 what do you have planned
now I think you're going to auction off
the the real one yeah the real one bro
like [__] has offered me 5 million for
the real one bro sold sold you mean bro
but this other guys like yo I'll give
you eight so it's like bro people are
like really so I might just hold on to
that [__] longer bro like get like 25
[__] bro I can get 25 bro I'll retire
after
that that's so for people that don't
know I was the first person that trusted
arlanta to paint a lamb yo lamb for real
hey yo the first one it's crazy he hit
me up he was like yo I'm going to do art
B I was at 2020 2022 2022 yeah so yo I
want I want to paint your Lambo on Art B
and I'm like dog I don't know sounds a
little crazy I'm like you know what [__]
it let's do two Lambos we then my hood
and then sensei's whole en oh yeah the
whole yeah yeah I remember that mhm then
we did the rose the dawn oh yeah that's
right the da look you know I have this
painting oh the
[Music]
Kobe Dam seen this one in a minute yeah
yeah Jordan gifted me this one yeah I
remember that and then the Muhammad Ali
Sensei has it at his yeah that this I
like this bro people love this people
come in here and they Tri I like the
spotlight under yeah that's hard you
know love
bro appreciate crazy bro proud all right
guys it's 5:30 they the ball in you got
to shoot it from there if now you're
blowing the
count what
[Music]
oh it's a little concerning how you just
have cars thrown in random places yeah
for I left this [__] here earlier good
thing we had the key in the wallet so
now we're going to go put this [__] to
charge hit the gym now
[Applause]
just finished the gym now we're going to
go get Jordan's drift car you guys don't
know don't know Jordan can't walk right
now and um his drift car has been in the
shop getting fixed we're going to go
pick it up for him and drop it off we're
going to go test drive the [__] out of
it to make sure that it's good and
potentially take Jordan drifting later
put him inside the car take him drifting
a bit if he's down if you can it's a
small car for a big guy I'm 6'4 remember
that all right Jordan you got your me a
all we got to take off the roof bro I
can't see anything with this whatever
the [__] this is like right in the
middle of it let's take it let's take
off the roof put it in the
Beamer and then let's test drive the
buck out this
[__] I don't think that's going to fit
bro it's going to fit
[Music]
[Applause]
can you like like can you get out of the
house and get put in the car um I I
could get in I'm I'm like I'm I'm hyped
up I'm down but then I was thinking I
was like crap like so we go drifting
like it probably will mess me up cuz I
think just even driving normal is you're
going to get moved around cuz that [__]
has no suspension you know that me yeah
sh has like bumpy as [__] you you feel
it right when you're yeah yeah but you
feel every bup from the road so we'll
just wait till you get better even if we
put a pillow right we can't no uh yeah
it's probably better not I appreciate it
though trust me
open
theu
yo yeah yeah push it up push it
up the [__] don't bre that [__] in what
is that open it up I think it's the
battery oh [__] back it up T put it
reverse T sh catches fire set don't
forget the next
trick all right guys market update it is
currently 9:29 in the afternoon I just
realized I don't think I've updated you
guys in the chart since like 10:00 a.m.
I think I could be wrong it's been a
long day let me show you guys currently
right now AUD CAD right now on the 30
minute time frame so earlier this
morning we were having this pull back
here and we were interested in taking
the position at this point I told you
guys that if we get the engulfing I
might be interested in taking it but it
just didn't look clean enough it just
didn't look like it's it if you guys can
see we have not taken any trays on the
100 to the mail count it's loed so
basically we we never ended up taking
the trade at this point right here
because it just didn't reject how I want
I get rejected but it's not how I wanted
to right so if you look at on the 1 hour
the 1 hour did have a dogee but no
engulfing so it didn't answer it there
there 2 hour didn't show any sign of
slowing down and the 4H hour just closed
obviously as a really strong engulfing
so I just didn't end up taking the trade
at all obviously played out very well in
my favor because I ended up avoiding a
loss which is phenomenal because the
original trade already played out which
is this trade right here so the original
trade that we wanted to take was this
one and it already played out this
second trade that we're taking here is
an add-on and it's a higher risk trade
and it's a trade that I don't tend to
take because the trade already played
out so there's no reason for to force
another trade into it which would be
exactly what this is right here next is
EUR USD so EUR USD we're having the
pullback we're having the pullback now
to this area of Interest I can almost
take these counter Trend trade to the
downside because as you can see it's
clearly forming the left head and the
right shoulder and currently if I were
to go down to the 30 minute time frame
you can see how it's having a very
strong accumulation and having UND
decision but if you look at the daily
time frame you can see how the daily
time frame has slowed down so clearly it
had a very strong breakout one day of a
dogee now we can very strongly fill this
so we can almost take this counter Trend
trade to this area right around here
something like this I don't know I'm
going to debate it whether I take it or
not it's a little bit of a highrisk
trade it is a little bit of a Dej trade
but it looks very clean look how clean
it looks to fill this right shoulder up
to this point so I'm going to decide if
I take it pretty soon right next GBP had
we already know the trade completely
went missed it there's nothing we can do
about it and then gbpusd it's still in
this channel got to wait for the
breakout so pretty much everything else
is nowhere near being ready the only
trade that I'd be interested in taking
is going to be AUD CAD once we have a
stronger rejection confirmation from
this level of resistance up here and
then Euro USD a little potential counter
Trend trade from this area to then here
to where then we would be interested in
then buying from here to the upside So
currently 9:31 in the evening let's see
if we can enter a trade tonight during
London so far no trade and it's Tuesday
it's a boring week so far it's been
pretty boring like I mean we've done fun
[__] but trading wise it's been kind of
boring sometimes you got to sit in your
hands I I don't want to say we got lucky
but we definitely did start The
Challenge on a hot week so we were very
fortunate to capitalize off of those
moves now we got to be realistic on how
more often can that happen and maybe we
don't trade this week at all maybe we do
maybe we'll never know but the market is
giving us opportunities as you can see
AUD CAD played out in our favor and GBP
CAD played out in our favor we just
happened to miss them so let's see if we
can catch your USD very soon all right
guys market update so I spent the
morning kind of just focusing locking in
diving on this trade to see if I was
making the right decision because we
have officially taken the most
degenerate trade of the whole entire
[__] chat the biggest counter Trend
trade it's such a d gen trade that I did
not risk 100% I risked 20% on this trade
so just show you guys currently market
update and we are negative about $500
because we literally just entered the
trade as the Candlestick just closed
right now so yesterday on Euro USD I'm
sure you guys can remember that I was
anticipating for price to have a sell
from this point up here to then reject
and then for price to actually make it
all the way down here to then have the
actual Buy on EUR USD because we're
anticipating for Euro USD to make it all
the way down here reject this level and
then head to the upside since we broke
out we never retested it so we are
expecting for that retest and here on
the 1 hour you can very very clearly see
that we are creating a potential left
head right shoulder again it's not a
confirmed right shoulder and so we don't
break under this neckline but I believe
what it's creating right here it's such
a strong level of accumulation looks
like a 1H hour double top 30 minute time
frame I see it I almost see it like
squeezing into this inwards uh triangle
whatever you want to call this again I
hate trend lines and I hate all this
stuff CU they're very subjective but you
can literally see how price is squeezing
into this area and I personally believe
it's going to have more of a reason to
burst down then burst up I could be
completely wrong because I don't believe
that this area that is rejecting from
right now it's going to be the area to
continue pushing to the upside I think
such a strong move like this has to have
a deeper retracement before actually
heading to the upside so when I go down
to the 4our this 4our Candlestick still
has about 3 hours to close and the last
one closes a very indecisive candle I
think this next one can engulf close
under this which then on the 1 hour
it'll give us the break under this
neckline of The Head and Shoulders if
you notice I put my stop loss
little bit right above this level
because if we pretty much break Above
This the trade is just going to keep
going to the upside so just to show you
guys how much that risk so this is my
effect book position size calculator so
we're taking Euro USD the account size
is 15,000 I rised about 20% on this
trade and then I have a 17 pip stop-
loss which gave me my lot size of
17.65 you guys can see right now in the
account we took a little extra lot
because
[__] it you know it's a little dj trade
you know I mean it's exciting these
trades are fun but very stressful like I
don't like this this not looking good at
all but whatever we didn't risk a lot
right we only risk $3,000 on this trade
all right next is going to be Euro AUD
so Euro AUD is finally having the
pullback so this is what we are
expecting for Euro USD to do so Euro USD
had the same push and we're expecting
this pullback to retest this structure
level to then head to the upside Euro
USD as you can tell same thing just
hasn't had that push down quite as far
as we wanted to so Euro AUD we are
retesting this level all I'm going to be
waiting for is a good rejection from
this area here the best way I can put it
is I'm just waiting for a break above
this right here break and retest above
that structure level in order for me be
to actually be interested in this trade
so for right now got to be patient on
your AUD and and then lastly AUD CAD
which looks like a very solid trade as
well I don't know I don't know if I want
to take this trade cuz I don't know if
this daily time frame can completely
close under after it came back and
rejected once again this level of
support this level of Support over here
to then now rejected to head to the
downside the only way I would I think I
would probably take this trade would be
if we get a a nice push like we got to
confirm that we're rejecting this area
so something like this then come back in
here retest it and then I'll enter the
trade right at this point right around
here so this not super excited about cuz
we missed the original trade but I am
liking a lot Euro USD which is obviously
the trade that we're in right now so
keep you guys updated it's 10:06 in the
morning currently we are down about $700
$800 actually we're down
$1,000 look at you good
oh that that doesn't seem very good not
good I mean I I called it you know I
don't really care um I'm glad that I
ended up getting that out of my system
I'm a [__] idiot bro like I mean
technically we're still in the trade
right so it could clearly reject this
level right here so I can literally have
the same reaction to the downside and
then this same reaction to the downside
that's why I'm very strategic with my
stop loss basement but the trade that I
should be taking is at the break and
retest from the neck line of The Head
and Shoulders like I know this I I know
this you know I just decided to want to
get involved but I'm not mad doesn't
really set us back much in the challenge
there's an unnecessary loss well not a
loss yet but it's just a trade update so
it's just like an hour later from the
last time that we took the trade
so yeah now we just got to wait and this
is what a lot of you guys do a lot of
you guys do this a lot of you guys will
take trades that you shouldn't be taking
but you guys won't put the blame on
yourself or hold yourself accountable I
know exactly what I did I did the wrong
thing now do I accept it 100% you guys
when you do the wrong things you don't
accept it you're ready to put the blame
on on someone's strategy on the markets
on anything but yourself that's what
once you start having that
self-recognition is once you start
developing a nonchalant character for
trading in the markets and that's how
you truly become successful because you
realize that your success whatever the
outcome is successful or not is 100%
because of you not because of another
Outsource like I'm the one that clicked
the sell button the phone didn't click
it just for me so for now set up for
good I can't do
this yo that's a sign that we
shouldn't we took the first [__] loss
in the 100 to the m
[Music]
come [__] man first loss of the 100 to
the
milk this my fault right like it's
nobody else's fault um I decided to take
a high risk trade and I knew it wasn't a
good trade so like it wasn't good
because I I didn't even posted so like
that's how you know I wasn't confident
So currently we lost $3,000 was exactly
what I calculated all within 1 hour and
the account right now is currently
sitting at
$122,400 um is not bad doesn't put us
that far away from where we were you
guys can see the trade literally as soon
as we took it went straight into stop
loss so that sucks um um so clearly this
trade is not valid so we just have to
wait for price to come down here to buy
audcad is the one that I am interested
in taking though we did have a very
strong rejection very strong closure not
interested in taking it quite just yet
uh I don't want to take any emotional
trades or any emotional decisions so I'm
just going to wait for a clean break and
retest under and then Euro AUD currently
we have rejected this level that's why
we got to wait for the break and retest
to take this trade
so yeah sucks right now it's currently
11: in the morning and uh we took the
first loss in the3 Mill probably what
we'll do now is just wait for these
other trade setups if that just continue
to go about the day really nothing
changes when you take a loss especially
the loss that was so stupid like this
one nothing should change at all I don't
have to go and meditate now I don't have
to then uh read a a book
noo [__] I've taken a bunch of losses in
the past it's just another loss only in
that sucks cuz it was a stupid loss so
we'll update you guys in the markets
what we end up doing and set don't
[Music]
forget oh [__] piece of [__] lost the
trade now we we got to get the roll to
the battery died on it you guys have
don't know changing your battery on a
Rolls-Royce Phantom is not that easy so
[Music]
got a Rolls-Royce they said it'd be fun
they it is fun I can't even
lie we got to get that fix literally no
luck has a nail you see that big ass
nail call me
Arnold m
ah almost [__] got a crap um [__]
with me so you guys can see right here
trade update it is currently a $5,000 in
profit and you you want to know what's
so annoying like I took that unnecessary
trade earlier over some dumb [__]
literally because I wanted to be part of
the counter Trend trade and feel like
I'm sniping a
pullback I should I should have risked
more on this trade and not have the
unnecessary loss but whatever we are
literally making back the loss right now
on AUD CAD exactly how I explained
earlier so we had the perfect break we
had the perfect retest we had the
engulfing exactly where it is I Look to
enter every single time and then our
take profit is set to this 4our
structure point right here which is
beautiful and it sucks because it
literally looking like the loss that we
took on Euro USD is going to be a wick
out which is super annoying and so
unnecessary and it does look like it's
still going to go down so this is just a
d trade lesson learned for the challenge
but AUD CAD is indeed looking very well
and then Euro AUD is having that
breakout exactly how I anticipated now
we just got to wait for the retest to
then head to the upside So currently
right now we are up about $4,000 putting
us back a little bit over profit where
we were before we made that loss back I
haven't made it just yet cuz we haven't
closed a trade but we're back up in
equity within the same [__] day set a
foret strategy for you hit the Subscribe
button you're going to keep missing out
on these trades all right boys trade
update before that let's appreciate the
beautiful weather of Miami today look at
this look at this let's come on let's
look at this
[Applause]
[__] the beauty comes after the
hurricane so that shows you guys that if
you're going through something hard
that's the hurricane that's the dark
time or as soon as that hurricane goes
through and you make it through it you
get this beautiful
weather and you get it beautiful in your
car when the weather's nice right oh
yeah I got I got another car so I got a
I just bought a you just can't say that
yeah I just bought another car I bought
a AMG C63 but I haven't bought it yet so
I'm going to go flip with uh coin with
Neil flip a coin for 45k or 35k
45k him 35k me so I haven't bought it
just yet but Neil gives it to me on my
face like my face car is worth money yo
but you see how motivation on that [__]
was yeah you got to go through the storm
to get the weather you got and then you
buy a new car and buying your car but
trade update currently we are sitting on
the account at about $5,000 in profit oh
wait no it's still loaded wait for it
wait for it $44,000 in profit so we had
a beautiful daily rejection Candlestick
from this area right here you can see
how the daily Candlestick had a pullback
and then rejected we go down to the 4H
hour I don't like how the 4our did not
close under this right here cuz now I
could reject this and then come up to
this area and then create a right
shoulder just like this one and then
head to the downside so I'm going to put
an alarm right around my entry to let me
know that price is indeed coming back to
my entry to see if it's then going to go
to the downside Euro USD just continuing
to the upside daily had a daily dogee I
still do believe this is going to head
to the downside I believe it's just
creating some resistance level through
here so we're just going to see if we
got Wicked out or if we were actually
completely wrong then Euro AUD we're
just waiting for this pull back daily
time frame had a beautiful daily dogee
rejection now we're just going to wait
for that Wick pull back into that level
to be able to catch an entry it'll also
be a little nice 4H hour higher low So
currently 7:15 in the afternoon I'm
going
go take another trade you know what I'm
saying so I'll see you guys later
tonight like at 10 10:30
so Center for I guess forget the walk sh
to the office when
you're
[__] so I I fig that it's deciding to
pull back because it's kind of setting
up for London session we're back here in
the markets let me just show you guys
right so Euro AUD it's having the pull
back exactly where we're anticipating it
and it's kind of coincidence well not a
coincidence but this means that the AUD
is getting strong strong right because
Euro AUD this is the quote this is this
is the base is the quote I don't know I
got to confuse that whatever but now on
AUD CAD this is going up because AUD is
getting strong so it's literally the
same move happening on both markets now
I'm pretty much taking the same trade
because if I take this long position
right here and I have it over here that
means that I predict that the AUD is
going to get weak and if I sell this
here to the downside I'm predicting that
the AUD is going to get weak so
coincidentally enough this pulled back
to a very strong level of support and
resistance to potentially reject from
exactly as Euro AED pulled back to a
very strong level of support and
resistance where it could potentially
reject from to head to the upside so I
think this pullback is actually a good
thing because it's confirming that price
is just having a retracement to create
that momentum for the next following
session which is going to be tonight
there in London So currently right now
time update it is currently 12 12:00 so
it's pretty much 1: in the morning well
not 1 in the morning 12 a.m. so
basically we're down about uh 1,400
right now the account is sitting at
about $10,000 in equity I'm not going to
close it I'm not going to modify I'm not
going to do anything I'm just going to
Simply set and forget what I will do
though is add a position here if it does
give me a nice bullish engulfing
Candlestick confirmation right at this
area so that I can actually take the
trade to the upside so if I got a
bullish engulfing here I'll take this
trade and if a bullish engulfing happens
here it should have a bearish engulfing
Candlestick here if you look at the if
you look at the candlesticks one 2 3 4
red candle right to the outside and then
if you look at this 1 2 3 4 red candles
it's literally the same move just vice
versa so this is how it looks up and
this is how it looks down like they
literally look [__] identical pin bar
doe pin bar dogee bullish
bullish bearish bearish
doe dogey literally the [__] same
move so if it happens on one it's going
to happen on the other now the question
is should we double dip or should we
just stay calm and only have one trade
we still got to hit the goal for the
week which is 30k and we're about 20,000
shy so we got to get to work so I'll
update you guys throughout the night so
annoying market update currently right
now 9:26 in the morning not good
currently we are down let it load let it
load $3,000 so [__] man all right so
last night price was right around this
area up here right on that Candlestick
and then we anticipated from that area
that we were going to have a rejection
which we did we had a beautiful
rejection from this area and then did
not work and price decided to continue
to pull back I don't know how we did not
get Wicked out I have no idea but we're
still in this trade and I'm I'm not
complaining if you go over to Euro AUD
we did have that bullish engulfing but
if you look at the time 3:00 in the
morning I was literally knocked out not
going to be up at that time I just
didn't really have to cuz I was already
in this position so this kind of
literally confirms that they both move
exactly the same and this one's pulling
back so I did not enter this trade this
is where I would have entered it and
it's kind of crazy because I think it's
going to actually pull up to this area
and then reject but it's a little bit
concerning because if it comes here and
then it rejects that means that audcad
has to go that little bit more to then
reject but I'm debating right I can't I
can't even believe I'm saying this this
is such a degenerate thing and going
against my trading plan cuz this because
of this right here look at this bro
yesterday we literally got Wicked out
for no reason if we show the trade
played out pretty much for the couple of
more hours it went a little bit more
into the stop loss but then boom the
actual move happen this is what we're
supposed to actually be entering the
trade right here at this breaking retest
of the neckline which I lowkey want to
but I need a better retest cuz that's
not an ideal retest but literally look
at this literally just because I had a
super tight stop loss and it was a
counter Trend trade this is why you
don't take these generate trades because
you don't know when this is going to
happen so if Euro AUD needs to come that
little bit more to this area to then
reject how it did here that means that
AUD cat ah oh man stop stop stop stop
stop stop stop yeah we're [__] so
whatever this we're just going to set
and forget might get stopped out very
soon Euro USD going to be waiting for a
little quick retest to then sell and
then Euro AUD going to wait for a
rejection from here to now enter the
trade so the trade is pulling back a lot
steeper than I would want it to and this
can probably play out sometime next week
so yeah this can probably be sometime
next week has not been a very good week
but you know what we're still ahead of
schedule remember we're on week four so
100 so week one is 100 to 200 week two
is 200 to 400 week three is 400 to 800
and then week four is 800 to 1600 2,000
so even if we get stopped out right now
we are still ahead by 2 weeks but is
that a good excuse to ruin your trading
plan
that is not a good excuse to ruin my
trading
plan you know what you're
[Music]
right trade up there boys we completely
forgot so I took the loss on the trade
and I said you know what done for the
day stupid loss bro I literally just
broke my trading plan so this is where
the account is currently right now we're
sitting at 8,000 900 well technically
$99,000 you guys can see here that we
were completely wrong in the TR
trade it is what it is go to here AUD
Cad and we were completely wrong these
are the type of losses that I like
taking I like taking losses that they
completely go in the opposite direction
I hate getting Wicked out and the trade
pretty much is going straight into
profit so I'm going show you guys my
fbook as well it's
loading by the way I have to have this
with me at all times my phone's growing
up all day so I'm have to charge it my
fbook is currently at
so now we officially have like a real
win rate real loss rate and stuff so
right now we're going to set and forget
for the rest of the day we got uh now
hold ourselves accountable for every
single time we take a loss so every
single time I take a loss I have to pay
a
consequence and I have that exact
consequence so it's going to make sense
in probably 5
seconds but literally every single time
I lose from this point forward I'm going
to hold myself accountable cuz I
realized that you know what I became
successful
and I became so consistent and so
disciplined because every single time I
would do something wrong I would beat
myself up for it I wouldn't just brush
it off and be like ah I won't do it
again if I do something wrong I pay a
consequence for it so I then don't go
and do that same mistake again and
that's what you guys are not doing you
guys are not putting yourselves in the
position of being uncomfortable so you
can then do what you don't want to do so
you follow what you have to do and I'm
going to do something that I don't want
to do but it's going going to force me
to do what I have to do and I'm doing
this leading by example show you guys
how real how legit I am because like as
I've gotten like really really
successful kind of Forgotten these
fundamentals and these basis of things
that got me to the point where I am now
so these unnecessary stupid losses kind
of make me reflect a little bit and I'm
always reflecting because I'm always
wanting to improve I don't ever think
I'm at the top or at the best point but
I think this next thing is it's going to
be very humbling and it's going to show
you guys how real I am about my word and
about always is getting better and
there's always a way to get better so
right now we're going to play a little
bit of basketball 7:00 and in like 5
Seconds you guys are going to see what
com so you blow the account and then you
blow the Porsche the most important
thing here is you got to have other rich
friends that pull up in another
[Laughter]
GT3 [__] dude yeah so L literally coming
in right now to through the gate I mean
I felt it on the highway I was racing a
Supra and I missed fourth gear so bad
like I missed this so bad I'm like it's
not that bad and I'm like I'm like oh
[__] this is worse than I thought and
then I just stayed in second gear the
whole way to here and now it just
doesn't go into gear at all dude like
got
all you smell the burn
clut all right guys so market update
trade update it is currently 11:10 at
night so yeah I just got home from doing
the transmission in the port
at least we're in the new C63 listen
this I love it but now we're going to go
pick up my new car cuz I just bought
another car I have a I just have a thing
for cars I literally go on Facebook
Marketplace and I just scroll and
whatever I like I just text them with a
lowball ass offer I'm like yo I want to
buy this right now and whoever replies
they reply fast enough like in the in
the moment I just buy it so I bought
this thing but then I realized you know
what there's a deeper purpose to this
car and I'm going to explain to it in
just a second once you guys see this car
because this is the car that's going to
hold me accountable to whenever I do
something wrong this is all going to
make sense in just one second so bear
with me I have owned
Lamborghinis Ferraris
Porsches
rolls-royces McLaren mlar bro McLaren
how can I forget about that but this
right here is GNA put the biggest smile
on my face the
biggest don't show them just
yet this right here is my
new
masterpiece
yes bro
it's perfect
perfect
oh we're getting a haircut on Thursday
night instead of tomorrow we always get
er Friday morning or anyone tonight cuz
Eric is not
[Music]
available what the [__] is that what do
you mean bro what is that [__] my new
cark you don't like it that's fake
that's fake just park up Park
up let me let me explain to you guys the
real moral behind this car right here so
this is so I follow my trading plan and
my trading rules obviously I have a [__]
ton of cool cars but this is going to
Humble me every single time I break my
trading plan this week I have broken my
trading plan twice meaning every single
time I break my trading plan I cannot
drive any of my cars for 24 hours the
only car that I can drive is this for 24
hours so what is that going to
incentivize me to do to not break my
trading plan every single time I break
my trading plan I have to drive this for
24 hours that's just the price and the
consequence that I have to
pay what do you think you [__] with it
stuff and it's manual it is yeah four
it's fourspeed where you going to drift
it that's just
1966 oh sensei's here give me a l you
don't like it
no
sorry hey hey hey hey you like
it we're going to be blessed if we get a
[__] whiip of air in
that no air bike oh
[__] oh
[__] all right all right all right all
right oh we out oh dude it's not that
bad at all
W this is
fantastic
oh yo it barely has oh my god oh it has
no brakes that thing is leaning boy is
it leaking no leaning leaning leaning
what way like this really
hey follow your trading plan if not
you're going to be like me oh
[__] oh
[Music]
[__] all right guys trade update market
update is currently 10: in the morning
um literally Market is about to close
it's Friday not much volume no trades
this is where the humbling begins you
guys know how much I Al driving my
Porche GT3 and driving it like a man and
driving my Ferrari and driving it like a
man but man's got to do what a man's got
to do and a man's got to pay the price
and I'm doing this show you guys I'm
holding myself accountable for breaking
my
rules and as you guys can tell I've
already attempted to drive this vehicle
and uh today starts the 24-hour clock
where I will only drive the beetle what
name should we give the Beetle keep in
mind it's a 1966 Volkswagen Beetle it
has the original engine four-speed
transmission tried turning it on earlier
it did not work we're going to try again
right now so this is to show you guys
that I'm going back to my roots of me
literally having to hold myself
accountable when I do something wrong I
don't want to do this but if I don't
follow my trading plan I will no longer
be able to drive a [__] Ferrari or a
Porsche I'm going to probably be driving
some [__] like this so I'm going to keep
following my trading plan so I don't end
up in a [__] car like this please
turn
[Music]
on what name should we give it should it
be a he should it be a her come on come
on
work way
up watch what do you guys know about
this we profit of Trader knows how to do
this
[Music]
colia col colia really that looks looks
sick how do you do it just praised one
side the side the most the most
important how the [__] the
important the most important you like it
I like actually sounds really good this
is not my security right this a student
but these guys are big as [__] bro go
all right so like so so this is this is
called a money true right as like many
people like probably know um but it
wasn't the point of that it's like a
money CH just so happens to be that way
the point is like I was explaining how
Alex is like famous in his own world
right and the trading world in the niche
but as far as like I you know like not
like LeBron right you're not like world
you know what I mean like you're world
but it's different right so the point is
that I see right he's doing the cigar
thing he's doing like I'll be watching
him cuz he's he's a good example like in
the community and just in general and so
the point of this plant right is that as
it stays in this pot it'll grow but it
comes to a point where this thing will
die because the pot is small so it's
just like in life right it's not always
about it's a people you surround
yourself with whether they are making
more money than you they're more famous
than you they have better Spirit than
you whatever it is it the point is that
you're you're you're growing this needs
to be in a bigger pot in order to keep
growing and I can show a picture I have
like three of these shits in my house Li
that's deep that is really but it was it
was on my heart for you bro for real I
believe like you know you've had time
you've had time your tree will actually
grow like full all together if you do
things really fast it'll grow tall but
it takes a while to grow the bottom
doesn't have a lot of support right it's
just like in life you know when you're
when you're going through you too fast
you going have distra I get it I get it
I get it another pod boy we got two
people that got shot this guy got
shot I was going to do this live but I I
just couldn't wait cuz I've had I had
before like I had money like locked up
in trade locker before and like it
glitched and I couldn't get it out
you're like so you're going to withdraw
100,000 right now
no no congratulations this my whip you
know all right yeah we only got space
for
two oh
oh yeah let's just push it let's push
it it's
[Music]
just finally got home from podcast with
the students it's
currently midnight about to be Saturday
technically so very long Friday did the
podcast with the cars drove literally
the car all day trust me I learned my
lesson and I'm going to follow my
trading plan cuz I don't want to drive
that piece of [__] anymore and the [__]
dope part is that I literally have to
park it somewhere here in my house and I
have no parking for it and I got to
figure out that mission probably just
thr in the back of the garage cuz I
don't plan to drive it anytime soon cuz
I don't plan to break my training plan
anytime soon so you going to Contin to
see this car so let me know a name of
what I should call this car because it's
going to be in the series until we
complete it and at the end we'll
probably just blow it up but I want to
do a little quick recap on what the
markets have looked like so EUR USD at
the beginning of the week we anticipated
for price to have a pullback to this
area of Interest we're still quite on
the way there we did have this strong
rejection Candlestick which ultimately
would have given us the trade that we
entered on EUR USD and it did did wake
us out for then the trade to almost hit
our takeprofit then Euro AUD we
completely avoided this loss on this
breaking retest even though we had the
pullback exactly where we wanted to this
is a trade that will definitely be
interested in taking next week on the
series AUD CAD you guys already know
this thing was just
completely unacceptable broke the rules
here chasing a trade simply because we
missed the first one for from here we
felt entitled to then entering on this
one bit Us in the ass GBP CAD played out
perfectly just was being very skeptical
and being very selective of the trade
that we would take and then
gbpusd never broke out of this downwards
Channel looks like it's going to do that
for next week and let me show you guys
the my effect book of where the account
is currently sitting at because we're
still technically ahead of what we're
supposed to be in the challenge but you
know kind of sucks being set back couple
thousand aage for no reason you guys can
see that this is a real account the
account is currently at $8,000 and you
guys can see down here in these stats
how we had seven total trades and our
profitability right now is currently a
70% Maj literally every single trade
that we have taken has been shorts so we
have not taken any long positions so
again it looks like we're being a better
seller than a buyer so good data to know
and I'd say this week out of all the
markets that we analyzed technically two
of them went in our Direction kind of
more or less and then the others just
simply did not give us an entry not the
best week in trading and we did manage
to still stay up and obviously not blow
the account completely because we're
being selective with the risk management
and like always every single one of
these trades I break down with my
students in the Sunday swings literally
the students that were with me earlier
from the podcast they have been on their
own journey of turning $100 into mil cuz
they just following mine one of them
turned $100 into 20,000 and another
turned $5,000 into $160,000 or the
students that I did the podcast with
today first how did you take the 4K to
the 100 okay okay I had 49 like 4,800
and I and I said you know um my goal
this week is 10K that was my goal is 10K
and I ended up getting to 13k were you
taking the same trades as me or your own
trades I I had taken a couple of your
trades and then I was actually taking
counter Trend trades too that's how I
was kind of like scaling the DJ trades
the DJ one what would you say to people
out there that want to become successful
in trading by flipping an account and
not going the prop route like what like
what would be the right way to do it I'd
say going into a personal Journey like
that it's really emotional having your
emotions right first and then knowing
you will take losses so you may have a
good four weeks and then where you lose
50% of the account but you have to know
that as long as you're standing with
your trading plan and learning from your
mistakes think anybody could do it that
has the interest in passion they're
literally following the same trades that
I doing every single Sunday I'm breaking
down with them and it's giving them
these results because they get on a call
with me and they find out these pairs in
real time when I'm interested in taking
them exactly where I'm looking to enter
exactly where I'm looking to exit so if
you want to know more about set and
forget and how how I can pretty much PR
predict these things all the time watch
the link in the video description below
because it is literally going to explain
to you what set and forget is and how it
lets me get results not so much like
this week but how I can still predict
the markets now the execution now that
goes you know factors in the the time
frame that I'm in uh the time zone of
the actual trade and that's something
that is part of the battle of trading
and wherever you are so if you guys want
to join c community and get access to
these trades make sure you guys click
the link in description below now what
we're going to do is fall asleep
for about 4 hours because we have a very
long trip to the Bahamas tomorrow on my
boat like comment and subscribe and I'll
see you you guys next week take care
guys